# ABHISHEK ARYAN

# Senior Software Developer

itsabhiaryan@gmail.com +91-8427440232

## **SKILLS**

- C++
- C#
- Kotlin
- Java
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 5
- Godot
- Android
- Cocos2d-x
- LibGDX

## **TOOLS**

- Android Studio
- Microsoft Visual Studio
- Unity
- Xcode
- Godot
- Git
- Perforce.

# **EDUCATION**

Punjab Technical University Computer Science Engineering, 2014

## LANGUAGE

Hindi ..... Native

English ..... B1 Intermediate

## **SUMMARY**

Over 9 years of software development experience in the full life cycle of the software development process. I am seeking a challenging position in a high-quality engineering environment where my resourceful experience and academic skills will add value to organizational operations.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mar 2022 -

## KEYWORDS STUDIOS, GURUGRAM

Present

Position: Senior Software Developer

**Project**: Card Based Multiplayer game supports crypto currency

Teach Stack: C#, Unity

Tools Used: Hansoft, P4V, Visual Studio

- Created different logical cards based on client requirements & bug fixes
- Chat system integrated along with some module

**Project**: Platform Port from XBox to PS5

- Move Windows API call to PS5 API
- Required implementation for PS5 platform

Dec 2018 to Mar 2022

PTW, HYDERABAD

Project: Plant Vs Zombie Free

Tech Stack: C++, Cocos2d-x, Cocos-Creator, Java, Obj-C, Android, iOS

Tools Used: Android Studio, Visual Studio, Xcode, Perforce

Position: Senior Software Engineer

- Worked on Unbundling of mini-game (A requirement to decouple mini-game packs into smaller packs and this is handled by the server.)
- Worked on a wrapper to handle different Ad SDKs for Android & iOS.

Project: <u>Bejeweled Stars</u>
Tech Stack: C#, Unity

Tools Used: Android Studio, Xcode, Perforce

Position: Senior Software Engineer

- Developed Henrietta Event from scratch and integrated.
- Wrote Automation tool using Unity Editor tool for creation of weekly/monthly/seasonal events.
- Released many technical updates which include supporting library updates like Ad SDK, Firebase SDK, and Analytics tool migration.

Project: Plant vs Zombie Hero

Tech Stack: C#, Unity

Tools Used: Android Studio, Xcode, Perforce

Position: Senior Software Engineer

Released different updates which include supporting library updates.

# **AWARD/OTHERS**

#### **Certificate of Excellence**

Awarded by PTW for outstanding performance.

#### **Open Source Contribution**

Contributed/Hosted many open source projects on Github.

#### **Technical Issue Resolver**

Active contributor on <u>StackOverflow</u> and developer advisor on the different technical issues.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Oct 2017 to Dec 2018

# MARKSHARKS, DELHI

Project: **E-Learning Application** 

Tech Stack: Java, Native Android, LibGDX, Box2D

Tools Used: Android Studio, SVN Position: Game/Android Developer

- Managed team to lead development effort towards the successful delivery of different project modules.
- Developed different interactive screens & integrated them with the main project.
- Apart from individual development I perform code reviews.

July 2014 to Sep 2017

#### **CONQUERORS INDIA, DELHI**

Project: Farm Fruit Village

Tech Stack: C++, Cocos2d-x, Native Platform Support (Android & iOS)

Tools Used: Android Studio, Visual Studio, Xcode, Git

Position: Software Developer

- Farm Fruit Village is a 3 match game that I developed from scratch.
- I used C++ and Cocos2d-x game engine to develop this game.
- AD SDKs, Analytics tool, IAP integration after core development.

Project: Bubble Shooter

Tech Stack: C++, Cocos2d-x, Native Platform Support (Android & iOS)

Tools Used: Android Studio, Visual Studio, Xcode, Git

Position: Software Developer

- A traditional shooter that I developed from scratch and further deployed in the different app markets.
- I used C++ and Cocos2d-x game engine to develop this game.
- AD SDKs, Analytics tool, IAP integration after core development.

Project: Ludo

Tech Stack: Kotlin, LibGDX, Native Platform Support (Android & iOS)

Tools Used: Android Studio, Xcode, Git

Position: Software Developer

- Asian board game that I developed from scratch.
- I used the Kotlin language and LibGDX framework to develop this game.
- AD SDKs, Analytics tool, IAP integration after core development.

#### Project: Spider Solitaire/Solitaire/Word Puzzle

Tech Stack: Kotlin, LibGDX, Native Platform Support (Android & iOS)

Tools Used: Android Studio, Xcode, Git

Position: Software Developer

- Card & Different puzzle games that I developed from scratch.
- Kotlin language and LibGDX framework I used to develop all the above games.
- AD SDKs, Analytics tool, IAP integration after core development.